<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://scriptdesigns.myshopify.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://scriptdesigns.myshopify.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://scriptdesigns.myshopify.com/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>ScriptDesigns - News</title>
  <updated>2016-04-30T07:42:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>ScriptDesigns</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://scriptdesigns.myshopify.com/blogs/news/105611206-surprise-sale-22-on-all-oracal-products-vente-surprise-22-de-rabais-sur-tous-les-produits-oracal</id>
    <published>2016-04-30T07:42:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2016-04-30T07:55:21-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://scriptdesigns.myshopify.com/blogs/news/105611206-surprise-sale-22-on-all-oracal-products-vente-surprise-22-de-rabais-sur-tous-les-produits-oracal"/>
    <title>SURPRISE SALE - 22% on all Oracal Products / VENTE SURPRISE - 22% de rabais sur tous les produits Oracal</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lyne Huneault</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>(Déroulez vers le bas pour le français)</p>
<p>It's time to pay our taxes so we need to increase our income! Starting now and until Monday night midnight, we are reducing prices on all Oracal 651 and 631 by 22%. Our Give Away contest remains active; for all $20's worth of purchase your name will be entered in the ongoing Give Away contest for 12 pieces of 1 yard of Oracal 631. Note that the 10% price reduction on Siser products continues at the same time.</p>
<p>You don't want to miss out on this sale; so place your orders now! Don't forget to enter your shipping discount coupon code. The codes are found on the Home page of our Website at <a href="https://scriptdesigns.myshopify.com/admin/pages/www.scriptdesigns.ca">www.ScriptDesigns.ca</a></p>
<p>Lyne and Tammy</p>
<p>******</p>
<p>C'est le temps de payer les impôts, alors on doit augmenter les revenus!! À compter de maintenant et jusqu'à lundi soir minuit, nous offrons un solde de 22% sur tous les produits Oracal 651 et 631. Notre accumulation de noms pour gagner un prix continue.  Ainsi, toute tranche d'achat de $20 vous donne une chance de remporter le tirage de 12 morceaux d'une verge d'Oracal 631. À noter aussi que le solde de 10% sur les produits Siser se poursuit <span class="text_exposed_show">en même temps. </span></p>
<div class="text_exposed_show">
<p>Placez vos commandes maintenant! C'est le temps de profiter des bas prix. N'oubliez pas d'entrer votre code de réduction pour les frais d'envoi.  Ceux-ci sont sur la page d'accueil du site au <a href="https://scriptdesigns.myshopify.com/admin/pages/www.scriptdesigns.ca">www.ScriptDesigns.ca</a></p>
<p>Lyne et Tammy</p>
</div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://scriptdesigns.myshopify.com/blogs/news/101695494-heat-transfer-vinyl-siser-easyweed-and-siser-glitter-in-stock</id>
    <published>2016-04-09T22:48:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2016-04-10T21:34:53-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://scriptdesigns.myshopify.com/blogs/news/101695494-heat-transfer-vinyl-siser-easyweed-and-siser-glitter-in-stock"/>
    <title>Heat Transfer Vinyl - Siser EasyWeed and Siser Glitter in Stock</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lyne Huneault</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><strong>HTV PRODUCTS – SISER EASYWEED AND SISER GLITTER  (Le français suit)<br></strong></p>
<p>As most of you who have been following us over the past 3 weeks know, we make every effort to respond to your requests for specific products.  You asked us for HTV and we are in the process of getting the full span of colours for both Siser Easyweed and Siser Glitter.  In a perfect world we would have all colours available by now but … the world is not perfect!!! </p>
<p>Our deliveries have been delayed by the latest Spring gift we got here, i.e. a nice snowstorm in April!  However, as of yesterday afternoon we had received 19 of the 34 Siser Easyweed colours (excluding fluorescent shades) and 8 of 16 Siser Glitter colours.  We hope to have the remainder of colours in stock during the course of next week but at this point, it is beyond our control. </p>
<p>Although we will not meet all of your expectations as of yet, we are happy to launch the colours we have in stock.  You will note that we are offering a vast array of sizes to respond to everyone’s taste.  Launching what we have now will also allow you to combine your orders if you were planning on ordering Oracal 651 and 631 while it is on sale this weekend. Please be assured that we will announce new colours including fluorescents as soon as they come in.</p>
<p>Thanks for you ongoing support and incredible patience.  You have no idea of what it means to us and we hope to be able to continue to provide you the best service at competitive prices.</p>
<p>Don’t forget to use your shipping rebate coupon codes.</p>
<p>Lyne &amp; Tammy</p>
<p> </p>
<p>****************</p>
<p>La plupart d’entre vous qui nous sont loyales depuis la création de notre boutique en ligne savent déjà que nous faisons tous les efforts possibles pour répondre à vos demandes spécifiques de produits.  Ainsi, vous avez été nombreuses à nous demander pour des produits HTV et nous en sommes à recevoir l’inventaire complet de toutes les couleurs disponibles dans les gammes Siser Easyweed et Siser Glitter.  Dans un monde parfait, nous les aurions déjà toutes à vous offrir.  Hélas, la perfection n’est pas de ce monde !!! </p>
<p>La livraison de notre stock a été retardée cette semaine par le cadeau printanier de dame nature, soit une bonne tempête de neige au mois d’avril.  En date d'hier après-midi nous avions reçu 19 des 34 couleur du Siser Easyweed (excluant les teintes fluorescentes) et 8 des 16 couleurs du Siser Glitter.  Nous espérons que les teintes manquantes s’ajouteront à notre inventaire au cours de la semaine qui vient : ce qui est par contre hors de notre contrôle à ce point-ci.  Pour répondre à la demande nous sommes heureuses de vous offrir à compter d’aujourd’hui les teintes que nous avons en stock.  Vous noterez aussi que nous avons voulu répondre à toutes les attentes en créant une vaste fourchette de dimensions.  Nous croyons qu’en mettant à votre disposition ce que nous avons en stock dès maintenant, vous pourrez économiser en profitant du même coup de notre promotion sur les vinyles Oracal 651 et 631 jusqu’à lundi soir.  Soyez assurées que nous vous informerons des ajouts à notre inventaire au fur et à mesure qu’ils se feront. </p>
<p>Merci chères clientes de votre appui et incroyable patience.  Nous apprécions sincèrement et espérons continuer à répondre à vos attentes. </p>
<p>N’oubliez pas d’entrer vos codes de coupons rabais pour les frais d’envoi ! </p>
<p>Lyne &amp; Tammy</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://scriptdesigns.myshopify.com/blogs/news/100848070-shipping-rebates-coupons-rabais-pour-frais-dexpedition</id>
    <published>2016-04-05T12:34:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2016-04-10T21:03:59-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://scriptdesigns.myshopify.com/blogs/news/100848070-shipping-rebates-coupons-rabais-pour-frais-dexpedition"/>
    <title>SHIPPING REBATES - COUPONS RABAIS POUR FRAIS D&apos;EXPÉDITION</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lyne Huneault</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><strong>BIG ANNOUNCEMENT - SHIPPING REBATES (le français suit plus bas)<br></strong></p>
<p>We know shipping costs are a pain! Since opening less than 3 weeks ago, we worked on different scenarios to help you, our clients with these costs. We believe this new approach is fair to everyone. Here it is!</p>
<p>We have created 4 codes for you to use on the checkout page. Note that only one coupon may be used per order. You must enter a code to get the rebate; the system will not do it automatically. The codes are:</p>
<ul>
<li>$5OFFSHIPPING This will apply an instant $5.00 reduction to your order of $50.00 or more (taxes excluded)</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li> $10OFFSHIPPING This will apply an instant $10.00 reduction to your order of $80.00 or more (taxes excluded)</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li> FREESHIPPINGCANADA Clients with a Canadian address will get free shipping for all orders of $125.00 or more (taxes excluded)</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li> FREESHIPPINGUSA Clients with a United States address will get free shipping on all orders of $150 Cdn or more (taxes excluded)</li>
</ul>
<p>If you have any questions or encounter issues with the codes, please let us know.</p>
<p>Lyne &amp; Tammy</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>NOUVELLES FRAICHES - FRAIS D'EXPÉDITION</strong></p>
<p>Nous savons que les frais d'expédition sont une vraie peste! Depuis notre ouverture il y a moins de 3 semaines, nous avons beaucoup réfléchi afin de trouver une approche qui soit juste pour tous. Alors la voici!</p>
<p>Nous avons créé 4 coupons rabais que vous pourrez utiliser pour réduire vos frais d'expédition. À noter que vous ne pouvez utiliser qu'un seul coupon rabais par commande et que vous devez entrer le code vous-même puisque le système ne le fera pas automatiquement.</p>
<p>Les codes des coupons rabais sont les suivants:</p>
<ul>
<li>$5OFFSHIPPING Ce coupon réduira votre facture automatiquement d'un montant de $5.00 pour toute commande de $50.00 et plus avant taxes.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li> $10OFFSHIPPING Ceci coupon réduira votre facture automatiquement d'un montant de $10.00 pour toute commande de $80.00 et plus avant taxes.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li> FREESHIPPINGCANADA Applicable aux clients avec une adresse au Canada, ce coupon éliminera vos frais d'envoi pour toute commande de $125.00 et plus avant taxes.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li> FREESHIPPINGUSA Applicable aux clients avec une adresse aux États Unis, ce coupon éliminera vos frais d'envoi pour toute commande de $150 Cdn et plus avant taxes.Les codes de coupons sont les suivants:</li>
</ul>
<p>N'hésitez pas à nous contacter pour toute question ou si vous avez quelque difficulté que ce soit avec les coupons rabais.</p>
<p>Lyne &amp; Tammy</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://scriptdesigns.myshopify.com/blogs/news/96474694-merci-thank-you</id>
    <published>2016-03-07T16:57:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2016-03-23T04:09:14-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://scriptdesigns.myshopify.com/blogs/news/96474694-merci-thank-you"/>
    <title>Merci / Thank You</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lyne Huneault</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>We couldn't have asked for a better response from all of you who have already ordered from us and given such positive feedback. I embarked in this new adventure a few weeks after retiring and honestly it certainly hasn't felt like retirement!  Both Tammy and I were hoping for a good response but never expected it to be as positive as it has been. Consequently, we wanted to use this first blog post to thank you. </p>
<p>Our focus is on client service and as such, please continue to give us suggestions on products you would like us to add to our inventory.  At the moment, I am working on adding HTV to our line of products and hoping I can provide you with some good news soon on this matter. </p>
<p>We have some exciting new products coming next week so subscribe to our newsletter to be the first ones to know :) </p>
<p>Did you know that you gain Loyalty Reward Points simply by registering on our site and some more for subscribing to our newsletter?  They quickly add up and will turn into savings for you. </p>
<p>"Stay tuned" as they say, we have more news coming in the next few days.  Once again, a sincere thank you.</p>
<p>Lyne and Tammy</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
